Finding Aid for the Elizabeth Vann Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- COLLINS DENNY PAPERS: INCOMING CORRESPONDENCE FROM M - W; VANDERBILT CONTROVERSY CORRESPONDENCE. (Box 46)
  - Folder 8 Incoming correspondence from Wilson - Wylie, 1903 - 1911
    - Wylie, Lollie Bell, 1909 Apr.8 (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - Letters of recommendation to L.C. Garland, Chancellor of Vanderbilt University, Oct. 1890, on behalf of Collins Denny for the position of Chair of Mental and Moral Philosophy: (Box 46, Folder 9)
      Noah K. Davis Univ. of VA
      James McCosh Ex Pres. of Princeton College
      John B. Minor Univ. of VA
      Francis H. Smith
    - Letters of recommendation to Dr. J.L.M. Curry for the position of President of Peabody Normal College, on behalf of Collins Denny: (Box 46, Folder 10)
      Beard, W.D. 1901 Jan.2
      Cowen, John K. 1901 Jan.7
      Davis, Noah. 1900 Dec.31; 1901 Feb.1
      Gray, Crane 1901 Jan.8(to Bishop Whipple)
      Gray, Joseph. 1900 Jan.4
      Head, James M. 1901 Jan.22
      (Mayor,Nashville)
      Hoss, E.E. 1901 Jan.8; Feb.14
      Howell, Morton. 1901 Jan.11
      James, D.M. 1901 Jan. 23
      Levering, Joshua 1901 Jan.8
      Lurton, Horace H. 1901 Jan.12(to Richard Olney)
      Olney, Richard 1901 Jan. 15
      Peters, W.E. 1901 Jan.30; Feb.3
      Price, Thomas R. 1901 Apr.5(2)(1 to Dr. Gilman)
      Stahlman, E.B. 1901 Jan.3, 13
      Whitehead, Paul 1901 Mar.1
      Wilson, B.F. 1901 Jan.14
    - Court Cases and Resolutions - Vanderbilt Universit Controversy 1910 - 1915. (Box 46, Folder 11)
    - Vanderbilt Controversy - Correspondence, 1910 Sept. 7 -1911 Dec.25, listed chronologicall, Sept.7 Martin E. Lawson (to Judge E.C. O'Rear); 1910: (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - Sept.7 Martin E. Lawson Cto Percy D. Maddin) (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - Sept.13 Percy D. Maddin (to Collins Denny) (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - Sept.14 Percy D. Maddin (to Collins Denny) (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - Sept.20 Albert W. Biggs (to Percy D. Maddin) (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - Oct.6 Percy D. Maddin (to Dr. J.H. Kirkland) (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - Oct.6 Percy D. Maddin (to N.E. Harris & Judge 0' (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - Oct.12 ? (to Harris & O'Rear) Rear (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - Oct.13 N.E. Harris (to Percy D. Maddin) (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - Oct.17 Albert W. Biggs (to Collins Denny) (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - Oct.15 Judge O'Rear (to Percy D. Maddin) (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - Oct.15 J.H. Kirkland (to Maddin) (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - Oct.15 Judge O'Rear (to Maddin) (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - Oct.17 Albert W. Biggs (to O'Rear,Harris,Maddin) (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - Oct.18 Percy D. Maddin (to Collins Denny) (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - Oct.2 0 James Cannon (to Collins Denny) (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - Oct.29 N.E. Harris (to Collins Denny) (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - Oct.31 Percy D. Maddin (to Collins Denny) (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - Oct.31 Percy D. Maddin (to O'Rear, Biggs,Denny) (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - Nov.l J.H. Kirkland (to John J. Vertrees) (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - Nov.2 Percy D. Maddin (to Collins Denny) (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - Nov.2 John Vertress (to Percy Maddin) (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - Nov.3 Albert W. Biggs (to Maddin) (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - Nov.4 ? (to Harris) (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - Nov.14 Percy D. Maddin (to Vertress) (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - Nov.15 Percy D. Maddin (to O'Rear,Biggs,Harris,Denny) (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - Nov.17 J.C Bradford (to Maddin) (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - Nov.21 Percy D. Maddin (to O'Rear,Harris,Biggs,Denny) (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - Nov.22 Percy D. Maddin (to same) (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - Nov.30 Percy D. Maddin (to Denny) (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - Dec.7 J.C. Bradford (to Maddin) (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - Dec.8 Percy D. Maddin (to Denny) (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - Dec.19 N.E. Harris (to Collins Denny) (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - Dec.19 J.H. Kirkland (to Collins Denny) (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - Dec.21 J.H. Kirkland (to Collins Denny) (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - Dec.27 N.E. Harris (to Collins Denny) (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - Feb.27 Percy D. Maddin (to O'Rear,Harris, Biggs,E.E. Hoss, Denny), 1911: (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - Mar.16 Percy D. Maddin (to Collins Denny) (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - Mar.28 Percy D. Maddin (to Collins Denny) (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - Mar.31 Albert W. Biggs (to Percy D. Maddin) (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - Apr.8 Percy D. Maddin (to Collins Denny) (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - Apr.13 Percy D. Maddin (to Collins Denny) (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - Apr.13 N.E. Harris (to E.E. Hoss) (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - Apr.15 N.E. Harris (to Collins Denny) (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - Sept.16 Stonewall Anderson (to Collins Denny) (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - Sept.16 S. Anderson (to Albert W. Biggs) (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - Dec.25 Judge O'Rear (to Collins Denny) (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - Vanderbilt Controversy - Correspondence, 1912 Jan.5 - 1915 Jan.12, listed chronologically (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - (1) n.d., 1912: (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Jan.5 N.E. Harris (to Collins Denny) (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - May 10 Percy D. Maddin (to Denny) (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - May 22 Percy D. Maddin (to Denny) (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - May 24 Percy D. Maddin (to Denny) (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - June 20 E.E. Hoss (to Denny) (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - July 10 Percy D. Maddin (to Denny) (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Nov.6 Percy D. Maddin (to Denny) (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Nov.9 Percy D. Maddin (to Denny) (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Nov.lif Percy D. Maddin (to Denny) (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Nov.30 Percy D. Maddin (to Denny) (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Dec.3 Col.A.M. Shook, Senator Luke Lea, & E.B. Stahlman (to Denny) (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Dec.10 Collins Denny (to Col. A.M. Shook) (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Dec.10 Collins Denny (to Sen. Luke Lea) (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Dec.10 Collins Denny (to E.B. Stahlman) (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Dec.10 E.E. Hoss (to Col.A.M. Shook) (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Dec.10 E.E. Hoss (to Sen. Luke Lea) (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Dec.10 E.E. Hoss (to E.B. Stahlman) (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Dec.10 J.H. Kirkland (to Col. A.M. Shook) (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Dec.10 J.H. Kirkland (to Sen. Luke Lea) (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Dec.10 J.H. Kirkland (to E.B. Stahlman) (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Dec.12 Collins Denny (to Col.A.M. Shook) (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Dec.12 Collins Denny (to Sen. Luke Lea) (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Dec.12 Collins Denny (to E.B. Stahlman) (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Dec.17 Col.A.M. Shook (to Denny) (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Dec.20 Judge Ed C. of Rear (to Denny) (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Dec.17 Col. A.M. Shook (to J.H. Kirkland) (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Dec.20 Judge 0'Rear (to Denny) (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Dec.24 E.B. Stahlman (to Denny) (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Dec.27 Collins Denny (to E.B. Stahlman) (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Dec.30 E.B. Stahlman (to Denny) (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Jan.1 7 Percy D. Maddin (to Denny), 1913: (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Jan.20 Percy D. Maddin (to Denny) (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Jan.28 Judge O'Rear (to Denny) (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Jan.29 Judge O'Rear (to Denny) (2) (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Feb.4 Albert W. Biggs (to Denny) (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Feb.24 Albert W. Biggs (to Denny) (2) (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Feb.14 Albert W. Biggs (to Denny) (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Feb.6 Albert W. Biggs (to Denny) (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - n.d. (1) (to Denny) (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Feb.27 Percy D. Maddin (to Denny) (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Feb.27 Percy D. Maddin (to Denny) (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Mar.2 Percy D. Maddin (to Denny) (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Apr.9 Percy D, Maddin (to Denny) (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - May 9 College of Bishops (to T.D. Ivey) (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - May 13 K.M. (to Albert W. Biggs) (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - May 19 Albert W. Biggs (to Denny) (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - May 27 Albert W. Biggs (to Denny) (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - May 28 Percy D. Maddin (to Denny) (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - June 10 Percy D. Maddin (to Denny) (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Oct.7 Percy D. Maddin (to Denny) (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Nov.21 Percy D. Maddin (to Denny) (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Nov.22 Percy D. Maddin (to Denny) (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Nov.29 Percy D. Maddin (to Denny) (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Dec.3 Percy D. Maddin (to Denny) (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Dec.6 Percy D, Maddin (to Denny) (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Dec.8 Percy D. Maddin (to Denny) (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Dec.19 Albert W. Biggs (to Denny) (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Dec.20 Percy D. Maddin (to Denny) (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Dec.26 Percy D, Maddin (to Denny) (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Jan.24 Albert W. Biggs (to Denny), 1914: (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - n.d. (1) (to Denny) (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Feb.23 Percy D. Maddin (to E.E. Hoss) (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Mar.13 S.C. Williams (to Denny) (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Mar.13 Percy D. Maddin (to Denny) (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Mar.20 Percy D. Maddin (to Denny) (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Mar.23 ? (to ?) The Vanderbilt (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Decision. (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Mar.24 ? (to ?) (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Apr.3 Percy D. Maddin (to Denny) (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Apr.6 Albert W. Biggs (to Denny) (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Apr.7 Percy D. Maddin (to Denny) (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Apr.7 Form letter (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Apr.9 Albert W. Biggs (to Denny) (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Apr.9 Albert W. Biggs (to Warren A. Candler- 2) (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Apr.11 Stonewall Anderson (to ?) (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Apr.13 ? (tot Anderson) (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Apr.13 ? (to ?) (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Apr.14 Albert W. Biggs (to Denny-2) (Box 46)
    - Apr.20 Stonewall Anderson (to A.W. Wilson) (Box 46)
    - Apr.21 Stonewall Anderson (to Denny) (Box 46)
    - Apr.25 Stonewall Anderson (to College of Bishops) (Box 46)
    - May 6 Judge O’Rear (to Denny) (Box 46)
    - Nov.12 Percy D. Maddin (to Anderson) (Box 46)
    - Nov.13 Stonewall Anderson (to Maddin) (Box 46)
    - Nov.13 Stonewall Anderson (to E.N. Harris) (Box 46)
    - Nov.13 Stonewall Anderson (to G.T. Fitzhugh) (Box 46)
    - Nov.13 Stonewell Anderson (to Judge O’Rear) (Box 46)
    - Nov.17 N.E. Harris (to Anderson) (Box 46)
    - Nov.17 N.E. Harris (to Anderson) (Box 46)
    - Nov.17 Judge O’Rear (to Anderson) (Box 46)
    - Nov.18 W.E. Hogan (to Judge O’Rear) (Box 46)
    - Nov.19 Judge O’Rear (to Anderson) (Box 46)
    - Nov.20 G.T. Fitzhugh (to Anderson) (Box 46)
    - n.d. (1) (Box 46)
  - Folder 14 - “An Act to Incorporate Trinity College” 1911 Jan.19 (Box 46, Folder 14)
    - Letter to Methodist Uniting Conference, Kansas City, MO, 1939 May 19, from Collins Denny - newspaper clipping. (Box 46)
    - Same letter, original copy. (Box 46)
    - Tombstone inscription. (Box 46)
    - (Pres.) (Box 46)
    - Conversation with Dr. Morrison/[of Asbury College, Wilmore, KY. 1941: Nov.16 - about refusing to become a member of the “new” Methodist Church. (Box 46)
- ELIZABETH VANN PAPERS
  - Folder 1 - Description of the paper doll collection (Box 47)
  - Folder 2 - Baby Carriage and Go-cart (Box 47)
  - Folder 3 - Newspaper articles from the Richmond Times Dispatch. Dec.7, 1973, Section D. (Box 47)
  - Folder 4 - The dolls and their clothes. (Box 47)
  - Folder 6 - Two pages from Memory Book kept by Edith Denny White and sent to Eleanor Ewing for use during a Delta Delta Delta celebration. Given to the archives Jan. 13, 1977. (Box 47)
  - Folder 5 - The doll house - a large scrapbook with pictures of furniture etc. for the various rooms. (Box 47)
  - Scrapbook about the D.A.R. Covers 1946-52 and the Continental Congress decision to eliminate discrimination. Made by Elizabeth in 1963. (Box 47)
  - BOOK: Form E Colore I Grandi Cicli Dell’arte. (Box 47)
  - BOX - 48 (large flat grey box)Diplomas, maps, photographs, scroll presented to Elizabeth by the WPA. (Box 47)
  - I. Diplomas (Box 47)
    - Eugene Ellis Vann - Bachelor of Divinity, Vanderbilt, 1907 (Box 47)
    - Eugene Ellis Vann - Master’s in Education, Columbia U., 1915 (Box 47)
    - Eugene Ellis Vann - Master of Arts, Columbia U., 1915 (Box 47)
    - Elizabeth Denny - Bachelor’s Degree, Vanderbilt, 1904 (Box 47)
    - Elizabeth Denny - Master’s Degree, Vanderbilt, 1905 (Box 47)
  - II. Maps (Box 47)
    - Virginia, Maryland, and Carolina, 1720. (Box 47)
    - Leicester, ,ass. - pertains to the Dennys of Combes, England (see Denny Genealogy by E.C. Denny. Ancestors of Sir J. Lional Percy Denny who was Lord Mayor of London around 1970). (Box 47)
  - III. Photographs (Box 47)
    - Waltham Abbey - given to Sir Anthony Denny by King Henry VIII (see Denny Genealogy. Book II by Dixon and Vann. (Box 47)
    - Jose Marti, Liberator of Cuba. (Box 47)
    - Wallace University School - Session 1895-96. (Box 47)
    - Honduras (?) (Box 47)
    - Unidentified coastline. (Box 47)
    - Quezaltenango, Guatemala, C.A. (Box 47)
  - IV. Presentation Scroll given to Elizabeth by the W.P.A. Historical Records Project, State of New Jersey, 1934. (Box 47)
  - V. Samuel Denny Family Tree. (Box 47)
  - VI. Books (Box 47)
    - Reliquias Historicas de la Esnanola by B. Pichardo, MCMXX. (Box 47)
    - Book handicrafted by the W.P.A. - contains photograph of Ellen S. Woodward, Assistant Administrator of the W.P.A., and her principal speeches, 1934-37. (Box 47)
  - VII. Wallace School Charter. (Box 47)
  - Add: Photographs (Box 47)
    - Graduating Class of 1904, Vanderbilt, College of Arts and Sciences. (Box 47)
    - Gymnaseo do 0”Granbery, 1913 (Eugene) (Box 47)
    - Wesley Hall Group or Kappa Alpha (Eugene) (Box 47)
    - Drawing of “Mark Twain’s Cabin” Jackson Hill, CA, by Blanding Sloan, 1938 (W.P.A.). Framed and autographed. (Box 47)
BOOKS IN THE COLLECTION
All About Spain. Georgia Long. NY: Duell, Sloan & Pearce, 1951. (From Eugene Vann’s travel books) BOX 59.5.
“America in Italy.” Preston Slosson. From Michigan Alumnus Quarterly Review, Vol. LXII, No. 14. Feb. 25. 1956. See F 15-20.
Belle Boyd: Southern Spy of the Shenandoah. Laura Virginia Hale. Warren Rifles Chapter, United Daughters of the Confederacy, n.d. See F28-15.
“Brief for Appellee and Cross Appellant, Atlantic Coast Line Railroad Co. United States Court of Appeals for the Fourth Circuit. #6200” William C. Chance v Atlantic Coast Line Railroad Co. By J.M. Townsend and Collins Denny, Jr. See F 14-15.
Chapter and Verse - 1: A Report of the Associates of the University or Virginia Library 1969-1972. Charlottesville, V”A: University of Virginia Library, 1972. See F 27-19.
“Chemistry and Psychology.” Edwin E. Slosson. (Address at Wittenberg College, Oct. 21, 1927, at the dedication of the Chemistry-Psychology Building) See F 35-9.
The Continuation of the Life of Edward Earl of Clarendon,,.by Himself. 3rd ‘ed. Oxford: Clarendon Printing House, M,DCC,LXI, Vol. 1 and 2. BOX 13.
“The Contribution of the New Physics to Religion.” Edwin E. Slosson. Address given at Park Avenue Baptist Church, New York, Nov. 6, 1927. See F 35-9.
The First Latin Book. William C. Collar and M. Grant Daniell. Boston: Ginn & Co., 1901. (Edith White’s book) See BOX 45.
Forma E Colore I Grandi Cicli Dell’arte. La Moschea di Cordova di Fernando Chueca Goitia. Sadea/Sansoni Editori. BOX 47
Hamlet. William Shakespeare. Tr. Dr. Domingos Ramos. Porto Livraria Charon, 1911. BOX 34.
Herblock’s State of the Union. Herbert Block. NY: Grossman, 1974. (A gift from Preston Slosson) BOX 16.
A History of the Meridian. May Ellis Nichols. Brooklyn, NY: ?, 1934. (A club Elizabeth belonged to) See F 27-6.
I Am Remembering. Bessie Craig Lowe. (A friend of Elizabeth’s, autographed) See F 22-7.
In Washington. Diamond Anniversary of the National Society, Daughters of the American Revolution, 1890-1965. See F 28-7.
The Lady of the Lake. Sir Walter Scott. Boston: Ginn & Co., 1890. (Used by Elizabeth at “Little Vanderbilt”) BOX 23.
Latin Composition for Secondary Schools. Benjamin L. D’Ooge. Boston: Ginn & Co., 1905. Parts I & II. (Belonged to Edith Denny White) See BOX 43.
The Lay of the Last Minstrel. Sir Walter Scott. Boston:Ginn & Co., 1889. See BOX 23.
Lodging at the Saint Cloud: A Tale of Occupied Nashville. Alfred Leland Crabb. NY:Bobbs-Merrill, 1946. See BOX 28.
M. Tulli Ciceronis de Oratore. Book I. W.B. Owen, ed. Boston:Leach, Shewell & Sanborn, 1897. (Belonged to Edith Denny White) See BOX 43.
Malawin. 1686-1936. Federal Writers report on Historical Collections, University of Virginia Literary Project 1949-50. Box 24.
A Manual of the Discipline of the Methodist Episcopal Church, South. Holland N. McTyeire. Nashville:Publishing House, Methodist Episcopal Church, South, 1904. (Belonged to Eugene Vann) See BOX 33.
Memoirs. Charles Long. 1 English copy and i Spanish copy. See Box 24.
My Eighty Years. Maria Brace Kimball. (1852-1933) Privately printed. Boston: Thomas Todd Co., MCMXXXIV. (A charter member of the Meridian Club, active in the Red Cross and army life) See BOX 28.
New Trails in Old Spain. Vernon Howe Bailey. NY:J.H. Sears & Co.,Inc., 1928. (One of Eugene Vann’s travel books) BOX 39.5
Novo Testamento. Tr. in Portuguese by Joao Ferreira d’Almeida. London:Sociedade Biblica Britannica & Estrangeira, 1930. (Belonged to Eugene Vann) BOX 34.
0 Livro de Job. Bazilio Telles, Tr. Livraria Chardron, de Lello & Irmao, eds. Rua das Carmelites, 144, Porto, 1912. (Belonged to Eugene Vann) BOX 33.
O.T. Denny, 1849-1949. (Oswald Thomas Denny, Teacher; Lynn Denny, son, b. 1885. Ruth Denny, dau., 1891-1914)See F 28-1?
Obras Completas. Don Pedro Calderon de la Barca. M. Agiular, ed. Madrid, 1945. (Belonged to Eugene Vann) See BOX 18.
The Origin of Lake Junaluska Assembly. Love Branner Atkins Shackford. 1965. See F 27-41
Standard Arithmetic. William J. Milne. NY:American Book Co., 1895. (Belonged to Edith Denny White) See BOX 43.
The Storv of Seattle. Roberta Frye Watt. Seattle:Lowman & Hanford, 193; Autographed) BOX 12.
A Short History of England From the Earliest Times to the Present Day. Cyril Ransome. London:Longman’s, Green & Co., T899. (Used by Elizabeth at Vanderbilt) BOX 25.
309 East and A Night of Levitation. Bianca Van Orden. NY:Harcourt, Brace & Co., 1957. (Short stories - autographed by the author) BOX 16.
Wedding Bells. 111. by Frances Brundage and May Sandheim. London: Raphael Tuck & Sons, Ltd, n.d. (A gift to Elizabeth in 1908) See F 25-9.
Western Breezes or Ballads of a Gringo. Randolph Henry Atkin. C.1914. (Written to friends in Colon and Panama - probably belonged to Eugene Vann) BOX 34.
TAPES
“Interview with Elizabeth Chapman Denny Vann by H.L. Swint and Essie W. Samuel for Centennial History”(of Vanderbilt University) Aug. 10 and 11, 1970. Tape-recording, 1 reel. BOX 32.5
“Recording by Edith White for her “Elect Ladies” for the 100th Anniversary of Centinary Church” 196?. Dictaphone tape. See F 43-5.
REMOVED FROM THE COLLECTION March 31, 1980
Centennial of the University - Program, Oct. 3, 1975.
Commencement Program, June 1, 1969
“The Lawson-Vanderbilt Affair: Letters to Dean Nelson” Aug. 1980
Perspectives on Vanderbilt. 1973
Proceedings of the Semi-Centennial of Vanderbilt University. Vol. 26, No. 3, April 1926
Vandervilt Alumnus. Vol. 59, No. 1, Autumn 1973; Vol. 59, No. 2, Winter 1974; Vol. 59, No. 5, Spring 1974; Vol. 60, No. 2, Winter 1975; Vol. 60, No. 3, Spring 1975.
Vanderbilt Calendar. 1975-74, 1974-75, 1975-76, 1976-77.
Vanderbilt Gazette. No. 55, Nov. 25, 1970
Vanderbilt Hustler. 1971: Feb.16, 19; May 7. 1975: Mar.16, 20.
Vanderbilt Today.
1970: Sept. - Vol. 10, No. 4.
1973: Feb. - Vol. 12, No. 7. April - Vol. 13, No.l.
1974: July - Vol. 14, No. 3. Oct. - Vol. 14, No.4.
1975: Feb. - Vol. 14, No. 7. Nov. - Vol. 15, No.5.
1976: Jan. - Vol. 15, No. 6. Feb. - Vol. 15, No.7.
Apr. - Vol. 16, No. 1. May - Vol. 16. No.2.
Oct. - Vol. 16, No. 4. Nov. - Vol. 16, No.5.
1977: Jan. - Vol. 16, No. 6.
“Vanderbilt University: The Commodore’s Best Investment” Harvie Branscomb, 1950
Vanderbilt University Quarterly. Vol. 5, No. 2, April 1905
Versus. 1971: Feb. 19, Vol. 3, No. 17. 1973: Mar.15, Vol. 6, No. 20.